Greta Stašelienė

JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

- in linkedin.com/in/greta-stašelienė
- gretatamasauskait3@gmail.com
- **2** +37063451498
- ★ Kaunas, Marijampolė
- o github.com/GretaStaseliene
- Final project: https://github.com/GretaStaseliene/Baigiamasis_ projektas

RELEVANT SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- PHP
- MySQL

LANGUAGES

- Lithuanian (native);
- English (advanced)

PROFILE SUMMARY

For the past 18 years I was playing basketball in many different teams with many different players. Recently I decided to change my career path and I tried programming. After completing Full-stack course at Vilnius Coding School I realised that I would like to start my career as a junior full-stack programmer. Therefore, I am currently open to new career opportunities in the field of IT.

EDUCATION HISTORY



FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Institution: Vilnius Coding School 2022-08-09 - 2022-10-11 8 weeks, 72 hours

In this course I have learned:

- Create websites using an easy-tounderstand and functional language HTML:
- Style website using the CSS language.
 Also Bootstrap framework;
- Make website dynamic with JavaScript;
- Learned how to build content management systems using PHP;
- How to work with databases using MySQL. Integrating PHP with MySQL. Secure data retrieval.

Link to my final project:

https://github.com/GretaStaseliene/Baigiam asis_projektas

Bachelor of Coaching Systems

Institution: Lithuanian Sports University Year of Graduation: 2016

WORK EXPERIENCE

· Teacher/coach's assistant

St. Vincent's Secondary school (2019-09-01 - 2020-03-05)

- 10 years of a professional athlete
- 18 years of a basketball player